1833 Frobisher Lane, APT 808 Ottawa ON. K1G 0E8 | +1 613 879 6164 | obabajide14@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over 8 years' experience of working as a freelancer and professionally in organizations. I offer a proven track record in several website marketing strategies, forging strategic partnerships, driving revenues and growing profits in competitive markets. I have a wide range of experience in designing and developing digital contents that help organizations stand out from their competition.

CORE COMPETENCY

- · Website Design and Development.
- · Graphic Design and Branding.
- · User Interface Design.
- Still and motion graphic design for digital marketing purposes.
- Search Engine Optimization and Search Engine Marketing(PPC).
- Social media strategy development and implementation.
- · Social media channel maintenance.
- Digital campaign performance reporting and analysis.
- Content Management System(CMS) maintenance.
- Knowledge of User Experience (UX) and Customer journey.
- · Customer Retention Marketing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JAN 2019 - JUN 2019 TRANSPARK LTD - SHEFFIELD, UK

CREATIVE LEAD

Transpark Limited is a Sheffield based digital marketing agency. I was responsible for the creative aspect of the business.

- Oversaw the design and optimization of the agency's website.
- Co-wrote and designed tailored content that increased monthly conversion rate. Strategized and developed social media contents to showcase and attract potential clients. More than 40% of leads are attracted via social media.
- Developed and designed digital marketing strategy and funnels to ensure steady monthly flow of income.
- Supervised outsourced creative projects to ensure brand consistency so as to attain the intended project objectives.

- Built and maintained client relationships by attending networking and referrals
- Managed Google ads to ensure maximization of the monthly budget.
- Supervised client's project from start to finish, ensuring objectives are met in a timely manner.
- Negotiated and managed all cost related dealings with vendors, freelancers, and clients.

AUG 2017 - OCT 2018

SHEFFIELD HALLAM UNIVERSITY- SHEFFIELD, UK

BUSINESS AND MARKETING ASSISTANT

The Materials and Engineering Research Institute (MERI) at Sheffield Hallam University is a dynamic interdisciplinary research institute dedicated to addressing industrial problems through the application of fundamental science and engineering.

- Interviewed and worked with academic staff to edit and update the MERI website. Created new content to increase the visibility of the MERI website.
- Tracked performance via Google Analytics and produced analyzed reports to increase engagement and performance.
- Identified MERI's target audience, collated information, produced promotional literature and gathered marketing tools for all internal and external events.
- Represented MERI at commercial exhibitions and events this included attending national engineering trade shows.
- Developed case studies for use in a variety of promotional
- materials. This involved interviewing clients and gathering images to fit each story.
- Promoted the use of blogging and social media tools for marketing purposes. Managed MERI's Facebook, LinkedIn and Twitter accounts.
- Collated letters and promotional materials for marketing purposes which were used to target MERI's clients.
- Monitored the MERI email inboxes and updated clients with ongoing inquiries. Responsible for sending out letters and promotional literature to prospective new clients.
- Updated and maintained IT systems, including grant capture and CRM databases, to support Business Development.
- Maintained a database of consultancy activity and helped to compile reports on the number and value of consultancy jobs and inquiries.
- Liaised with academic staff and collated timesheets for projects.
 Worked with the Business Development Manager in regard to the marketing, development and administration of the ERDF funded Sheffield Innovation Programme.
- Managed several interns on consultancy projects and assisted in report delivery.
- Communicated with companies to ensure validity and completeness of data held on databases
- Created and processed expense claims, purchase orders and invoices.
- Supported and interacted with the MERI admin team on issues pertaining to MERI marketing, business development and the MERI website.

LEO OLOWOOKERE 2

DEC 2015 - AUG 2016 BIG MULTIQUEST CONCEPT LTD - OYO, NG

OPERATION EXECUTIVE

This is a Nigerian based haulage company, that provides a high quality haulage and distribution services across cities in Nigeria.

- Scheduled and coordinated meetings, appointments, and travel arrangements for supervisors and managers
- Maintained detailed administrative and procedural processes to improve accuracy and efficiency.
- Evaluated operational records and scheduled adjustments to maximize efficiency.
- Established transportation cost standards and economical delivery practices.
- Analyzed cost implication of vehicles to be repaired.
- Constantly improved Website user interphase and user Experience design to increase engagement.
- Designed media content for digital and marketing purposes.
- Managed medical supply inventory, insurance records, staff charts and files.
- Drafted budgets, monitored costs and reduced company's expenses
- Updated staff and client's profile on the intranet portal.
- Liaised and engaged with clients and potential clients to ensure business continuity.

DEC 2014 - NOV 2015

TRANSCORP HOTEL - CALABAR, NG

IT OFFICER

Transcorp Hotels Calabar(THC) is an arm of Transcorp Hotels in Nigeria. THC properly reflects the rich culture and history of the region while creating unforgettable experiences for savvy travellers and tourists.

- Rendered first level IT support to Staff and Guests in the hotel.
- Installed Audio/Visual equipment for meetings and events within the hotel
- Maintained and developed website pages, graphic and multimedia for digital marketing platforms.
- Worked with the ICT manager to suggest and work on design enhancement to the hotel's website.
- Designed promotional materials for the hotel's events and marketing activities.
- Tracked and reported the hotel's website performance on a quarterly basis.
- Worked with stakeholders to service their design requirements
- Analyzed and restored computer system faults within the hotel.

EDUCATION

SEP 2016 - OCT 2018 SHEFFIELD HALLAM UNIVERSITY

MBA (Master of Business Administration)

SEP 2008 – JULY 2013 LADOKE AKINTOLA UNI. OF TECHNOLOGY

COMPUTER SCIENCE . B.Tech

LEO OLOWOOKERE 3

LEO OLOWOOKERE 4